presidentialserviceawards.gov 2012-10-14

# President's Volunteer Service Award

Effective at midnight October 1st the President's Volunteer Service Award website will be closed for annual repairs, update and maintenance. The site will be down from October 1st - 31st re-opening November 1, 2012. If you have any questions please contact our customer service team at 866-545-5307.

#### Privacy

President’s Volunteer Service Award (the "PVSA WEB SITE") has adopted and implemented this privacy policy as part of our commitment to protecting your personal information from misuse. While this policy focuses on online collection of information related to your interaction with the PVSA WEB SITE's website (the "website"), it applies to the PVSA WEB SITE's collection policies in general. 

###### What information does the PVSA WEB SITE collect?

The website's registration, online surveys, contest and product order forms may ask users to provide personally identifiable information in one of three ways: through contact information (including, without limitation, name, address, phone number (home, work and/or cell), fax number and e-mail address), demographic information (including, without limitation, race, gender, ethnicity, and age) and, in some cases, financial information (including, without limitation, organizational income (when on behalf of an organization) and credit card number (when on behalf of an individual)). Some information will be required for you to avail yourself of that particular feature of the website. None of this personally identifiable information will be shared with third parties or used to market third party products or services; it will only be used as described below. 

From time to time, we may use the standard "cookie" feature of major browser applications that allows us to store data about your visit. Cookies help us learn which areas of our site are useful and which areas need improvement. We do not set any personally identifiable information in cookies, nor do we employ any data capture mechanisms on our website other than cookies. You may configure your web browser to prevent cookies from being set on your computer. 

The PVSA WEB SITE may also gather anonymous, or aggregate, information, which may be used by us or shared with third parties. This is information which does not personally identify you, but which may be helpful for marketing purposes or for improving the services we offer. Generally, this information is collected through "traffic data" and may entail the use of numeric codes used to identify a computer. 

###### What does the PVSA WEB SITE do with collected information?

We use personally identifiable information from our online registration, survey, contest and order forms to send you information about the PVSA WEB SITE and its various projects and initiatives, or to communicate with you about a project in which you are participating. If you supply contact information, it may also be used to contact you for other purposes. 

We may use cookies to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, and for other purposes. 

The PVSA WEB SITE may use your IP address (the number assigned to your computer while it is on the Internet) to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. If you shop on the website, your IP address may be used to help identify your computer and your online "shopping cart" and to gather broad demographic information. If you submit financial information, it will be used to check your qualifications and to bill you for products and services you have ordered. 

The PVSA WEB SITE may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on the PVSA WEB SITE or its subsidiaries or affiliates; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of the PVSA WEB SITE or the users of this website, and (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of the website's users. 

###### What type of public forums are available through the website?

We may make various public forums (such as chat rooms) and functions available to you. During these activities, you will have the option to add additional personal information that is beyond the information gathered at registration. Any information you choose to share when using any of these forums or functions becomes public information. It is incumbent upon you to exercise caution in deciding whether to disclose such information.   
Does the PVSA WEB SITE control the practices of sites to which it links?  
This website contains links to other websites. We have no control over, and are not responsible for, the privacy policies, reliability or content of such sites.   

###### How does the PVSA WEB SITE protect children's information?

The PVSA WEB SITE respects the sensitive nature of children's privacy online. We are a general audience site, and do not direct our content specifically at children under thirteen (13) years of age. If the PVSA WEB SITE learns that a user is under age 13, the PVSA WEB SITE will delete the child's information from our systems. 

###### Can I opt out of allowing the PVSA WEB SITE to use my personally identifiable information?

The PVSA WEB SITE allows you to remove your information from our database in order to stop receiving future communications from the PVSA WEB SITE or by contacting us at [privacy@presidentialserviceawards.gov](mailto:privacy@presidentialserviceawards.gov "Email here if you like to remove your information from PVSA database"). 

###### What type of security does the website employ?

The website uses encrypted authentication technology when you login to the website in an effort to provide a secure environment that is protected from third party access, alteration, theft or misuse of the personal information gathered or confirmed at registration.

###### How can I update my information?

The PVSA WEB SITE gives you the opportunity to change or modify information you have previously provided by sending an e-mail to [privacy@presidentialserviceawards.gov](mailto:privacy@presidentialserviceawards.gov "Email here to change/modify your information from PVSA database") or calling (866) 545-5307. 

###### How can I contact the PVSA WEB SITE?

If you have any questions about this privacy your interaction with website, please feel free to contact us at [privacy@presidentialserviceawards.gov](mailto:privacy@presidentialserviceawards.gov "Email here to ask about Privacy in PVSA web site"). 

Any of the policies or procedures above may be changed at any time without prior notice.
